National Arts Club
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Printed Matter, 1893-1960, undated, Series 8:
  - National Arts Club Printed Matter, circa 1900-1960, undated, 8.1:
    The subseries also contains announcements, invitations, tickets, entry blanks, and artist prospectuses; and programs relating to concerts, social activities, meetings of the Men's Open Table, and anniversary celebrations. Speeches include "Tribute to William Winter," 1909; "Social Art, an Address Delivered to The Open Table by F.W. Ruckstuhl," 1915; and "The Tilden Mansion, Home of the National Arts Club," by Charles Rollinson Lamb, 1932. Miscellaneous publications include "Forty Seven Facsimile Drawings by American Artists," by the American Artists' War Emergency Fund, 1918; "What Europe Thinks of American Art, Eminent Opinions Compiled by Henry Rankin Poore, A.N.A.," circa 1930; and printed pictures (reproductions of photographs).
    - Constitution, By-laws, and House Rules, 1940-1959, undated (Reel 4260, Frame 156-203)
    - Yearbooks, 1901-1905/06; 1911-1915/16;1917/18-1921/22; 1923/24; 1930/31 (Reel 4260, Frame 204-790)
    - Membership Lists (see also Series 4: Membership; Series 8.1: National Arts Club Printed Matter, Yearbooks; and Series 8/2: Non-National Arts Club Printed Matter, Club Members of New York), circa 1900-1951 (Reel 4260, Frame 791-975)
    - Bulletin [title varies slightly], 1907-1901; 1914; 1919-1920; 1924; 1928-1958; 1960 (Reel 4260, Frame 976-1138)
    - Bulletin, 1907-1901; 1914; 1919-1920; 1924; 1928-1958; 1960, cont. (Reel 4261, Frame 7-997)
    - Brochures, 1898-circa 1960 (Reel 4261, Frame 998-1082)
    - Treasurer's Reports, 1902-1955/56 (Reel 4261, Frame 1083-1110)
    - Treasurer's Reports, 1902-1955/56, cont. (Reel 4262, Frame 8-44)
    - Exhibition Catalogs and Related Printed Matter (see also Appendix A), 1900-1960, undated (Reel 4262, Frame 85-321)
    - Events (see also Series 2.8: Men's Open Table), 1912-1960, undated (Reel 4262, Frame 322-431)
    - Speeches (see also Series 6: Miscellaneous, Speeches), 1909-1932 (Reel 4262, Frame 45-84)
    - Miscellaneous Publications, 1918-circa 1930 (Reel 4262, Frame 432-556)
  - Non-National Arts Club Printed Matter, 1893-1959, undated, 8.2:
    Volume 8 of Club Members of New York in this subseries contains a list of club members. Additional lists can be found in Series 8.1: National Arts Club Printed Matter, Membership Lists and Yearbooks; and Series 4: Membership. Printed matter concerning other art organizations includes a general brochure of the Artist-Artisan Institute, undated, and extracts from speeches delivered at the initial meeting of the National Commission to Advance American Art, 1933. The records relating to Gramercy Park include a copy of "The Gramercy Glide," a song and dance dedicated to the National Arts Club.
    - Club Members of New York, vol. 8, 1924 (Reel 4262, Frame 557-568)
    - By and About NAC Members (Reel 4262, Frame 569-646)
    - About Gramercy Park (Reel 4262, Frame 647-662)
    - Exhibition Announcements, Catalogs, etc., 1916-1955, undated (Reel 4262, Frame 663-716)
    - Other Art Organizations (Reel 4262, Frame 717-738)
    - Miscellaneous, Art Matters (Reel 4262, Frame 739-762)
    - Miscellaneous, Not Art Matters (Reel Unfilmed)
    - Loose Clippings, 1893-1959, undated (Reel 4262, Frame 764-1090)
- Scrapbooks, 1898-1940, Series 9:
  This series contains seventeen scrapbooks complied by the National Arts Club. They include Annual Club Record, 1908-1912 (3 volumes); National Arts Club Printed Matter, 1898-1940 (7 volumes); and Clippings, 1912-1940 (7 volumes). Titles of NAC exhibition catalogs are noted. For additional records in this category see also Series 8: Printed Matter and Appendix A.
  The series is organized into three subseries:
  9.1: Annual Club Record, 1898-1912
  9.2: National Arts Club Printed Matter, 1898-1940
  9.3: Clippings, 1912-1940
  - Annual Club Record, 1898-1912, 9.1:
    These scrapbooks contain a variety of NAC printed matter, including Bulletin, the yearbook, membership lists, by-laws, constitution, house rules, catalogs, invitations, and programs; clippings regarding entertainments and club social events, exhibitions, obituaries, and articles about members.
    - Volume 1, 1898-1909 (Reel 4263, Frame 6-158)
      Members Fall Sketch Exhibition, Oct. 21- Nov. 7, 1908
      International Exhibition of Pictorial Photography, Feb. 2-20, 1909
      John W. Alexander Retrospective, Feb. 23-March 17, 1909
    - Volume 2 [target omitted], 1909-1910 (Reel 4263, Frame 159-208)
      Fourth Annual Exhibition of Books of the Year, Nov. 3-26, 1909
      Exhibition of the Former Students of the Art Students League, May 1910
    - Volume 3, 1911-1912 (Reel 4263, Frame 209-319)
      First Annual Exhibition of Artist Life Members, Jan. 5-Feb. 3, 1911
      Walter Shirlaw Memorial, March 8-April 5, 1911
      Third Annual Exhibition of Advertising Art, Oct.20-Nov. 19, [1911?]
      Group Exhibition, April 1911
      First Prize Exhibition of Artist Life Members, Jan. 3-28, 1912
      Otto Walter Beck, Jan. 31-Feb. 18, 1912
      Etchings of E. T. Hurley, Feb. 21-March 10, 1912
      National Park Pictures Collected and Exhibited by the Department of the Interior, March 13-20, 1912
      Exhibition of Paintings, Embroideries and Tapestries from the Collection of Mr. Emerson McMillan, April 4-21, 1912
      Exhibition of Original Dickens and Thackeray Drawings by Harry Furniss, April 24-May 4, 1912
      Special Sculpture Exhibition, May 8-June 1, 1912
  - National Arts Club Printed Matter, 1898-1940, 9.2:
    - Volume 4, 1898-1907 (Reel 4263, Frame 321-586)
      Portraits of Napoleon owned by John Leonard Dudley, Jan. 1903
      Loan Exhibition of Pictures by Eminent American Painters, Jan. 5-16, 1904
      Loan Exhibition of Pictures by American Figure Painters, March 2-15, 1904
      Loan Exhibition of Pictures by Robert Henri, William Glackens, George Luks, Arthur B. Davies, and Maurice Prendergast, Jan. 5-16, 1904
      Loan Exhibition of Pictures by Some Boston Artists, April 5-15, 1904
      Loan Exhibition of Pictures by Old Masters, from Durand-Ruel, April 9-30, 1904
      Loan Exhibition of Paintings, Water Colors and Drawings by John La Farge, May 3-14, 1904
      Municipal Art Society Exhibit of Poster Designs, April 2-14, 1906
      Opening Exhibition of American Paintings from the Collection of Mr. William T. Evans, Nov. 8-18, 1906
      Exhibition by Some American Artists, Dec. 18, 1906-Jan. 1, 1907
      Modern German Paintings from the Collection of Hugo Reisinger, Jan. 12-Feb. 1, 1907
      Sixth Annual Exhibition of the Municipal Art Society of New York, March 13-31, 1907
      Wood-Engravings of Timothy Cole made for Century Magazine, May, 1907
      Exhibitions of Artists' Preliminary Sketches, May 1907
      Fall Exhibition of Sketches by Members, Oct. 16-Nov. 16, 1907
    - Volume 5, 1906-1911 (Reel 4263, Frame 587-744)
      Exhibition of Some American Artists, Dec. 18, 1906-Jan. 18, 1907
      Exhibition of Artists' Preliminary Sketches, May 1907
      Contemporary Paintings, Feb. 1-15, 1908
      Contemporary Art, Jan. 4-25, 1908
      Special Exhibition of Members' Work, April 2-25, 1908
      Paintings Loaned by C. C. Ruthrauff, April 25-May 15, 1908
      Members' Special Exhibition, April 15-May 8, 1908
      Members' Fall Sketch Exhibition, Oct. 21-Nov. 7, 1908
      Fourth Annual Book Exhibition, Nov. 3-26, 1909
      Louis Mark of Budapest, March 2-28, [1910?]
      Alfred East of London, April 6-30, 1910
      Exhibition of Former Students of the Art Students League, May 4-Oct. 10, 1910
      Third Annual Exhibition of Advertising Art, Oct. 20-Nov. 1,1910
      Walter Shirlaw Memorial Exhibition, March 8-April 5, 1911
      Group Exhibition of Paintings by William R. Derrick, Reynolds Beal, Gifford Beal, and Frederick J. Waugh, April 1911
    - Volume 5, cont. (Reel 4264, Frame 7-184)
    - Volume 6, 1911-1917 (Reel 4264, Frame 186-706)
      Special Prize Exhibition, Jan. 3-28, 1912
      Sculpture Exhibition, May 8-June 1, 1912
      Third Special Exhibition of the Society of Illustrators, Oct.-Nov. 1912
      Exhibition of Works by the Late Frederick Warren Freer, Feb. 12-March 9, 1913
      Work of Painter, Sculptor, and Architect Members, Jan. 7-Feb. 1, 1914
      Contemporary Art, Feb. 5-March 7, 1914
      Portraits, March 3-24, 1915
      Work of Painter Members, Jan. 5-18, 1916
      Forty-ninth Annual Exhibition of the American Water Color Society, Feb. 3-27, 1916
      Loan Exhibition of Portraits of Academicians and Associates Selected from the Permanent Collection of the National Academy of Design, March 2-25, 1916
      One Hundred American Paintings by the American Institute of Graphic Arts, March 28-April 14, 1916
      Exhibition of American Prints, March 28-April 14, 1916
      Members' Summer Sketch Exhibition, June-Aug. 1916
      Annual Exhibition of the Work of Artist Members, Jan. 4-26, 1917
      Fiftieth Annual Exhibition of the American Water Color Society, Feb. 1-24, 1917
      Etchings by Contemporary Artists, under the auspices of the American Institute of Graphic Arts, Feb. 28-March 23, 1917
      Paintings by Boston Artists, March 29-April 28, 1917
      Members' Annual Sketch Exhibition, May-Sept. 1917
    - Volume 7, 1917-1924 (Reel 4264, Frame 707-1073)
      The Netherlands Exhibition, Oct. 3-31, 1917
      Annual Exhibition of the Work of Artist Members, Jan. 3-Feb. 1, 1918
      Fifty-first Annual Exhibition of the American Water Color Society, Feb. 7-March 1, 1918
      Summer Sketch Exhibition, June-Oct. 1918
      Retrospective Exhibition of Work of Artist Life Members, Jan. 8-31, 1919
      Special Exhibition of the Society of Illustrators, April 2-May 3, 1919
      Members' Annual Sketch Exhibition, May-Oct. 1919
      Annual Exhibition of Painter and Sculptor Members, Jan. 7-30, 1920
      Special Exhibition of the Society of Illustrators, March 31-April 16, 1920
      Members' Summer Exhibition of Sketches and Small Sculpture, Jun-Oct. 1920
      Exhibition of Art Expression by Club Members, Dec. 1-29, 1920
      Annual Prize Exhibition, Jan. 5-27, 1921
      First Annual Exhibition of the Art Directors Club of New York, March 2-13, 1921
      Humorists Exhibition, Dec. 7-30, 1921
      Annual Prize Exhibition of Painter and Sculptor Members, Jan. 5-28, 1922
      Exhibition of Paintings by Charles C. Curran, Franklin deHaven, George Glenn Newell, Harry Watrous, Feb. 15-March 5, 1922
      Loan Exhibition of American Paintings Owned by Club Members, April 5-30, 1922
      Annual Prize Exhibition of Painter and Sculptor Members, June 5-28, 1922
      Summer Exhibition of Members' Work, May-Oct. 1922
      Special Exhibition of Members' Work, Dec. 6-29, 1922
      Annual Prize Exhibition, Jan. 10-Feb. 10, 1923
      Humorists Exhibition, Feb. 14-March 3, 1923
      Group Exhibition: Hayley Lever, Leon Dabo, William R. Derrick, Charles P. Gruppe, Charles Robert Patterson, April 1923
      Exhibition of Living American Etchers, Dec. 12-29, 1923
      Members' Annual Exhibition, Jan. 9-Feb. 2, 1924
      Exhibition of Sculpture, March 5-29, 1924
      Exhibition of Books Illustrating the History of Printing, April 30-May 15, 1924
    - Volume 7, cont. (Reel 4265, Frame 7-316)
    - Volume 8, 1924-1932 (Reel 4265, Frame 318-1159)
      Exhibition of Art Expression by Club Members, Dec. 1-29, 1924
      Members' Annual Exhibition, Jan. 7-31, 1925
      Autograph Letters with Accompanying Portraits of Authors, Statesmen, Artists, etc., Feb. 23-March 7, 1925
      Second Annual Exhibition of Living American Etchers, Dec. 10-27, 1924
      Special Exhibition of Lithographs, Woodblocks, and Linoleum Cuts, April 8-May 9, 1925
      Exhibition of Living American Etchers, Dec. 3-20, 1925
      Members' Annual Exhibition, Jan. 13-Feb. 6, 1926
      Special Group Exhibition, Feb. 10-27, 1926
      Special Exhibition of Copies of Old Masters, March 3-27, 1926
      Special Exhibition of Architecture, Sculpture, and Decorative Painting, April 7-May 7, 1926
      Fifth Annual Exhibition of the Brooklyn Society of Etchers, May 1926
      Exhibition of Volkbehr Collection of Incunabula, Aug. 23-Sept. 30, 1926
      Summer Exhibition, 1926
      Fourth Annual Exhibition of Living American Etchers, Dec. 2-22, 1926
      Members' Annual Exhibition, Jan. 5-29, 1927
      Exhibition and Auction of Works of Art by Artist Members, Feb. 11-27, 1927
      Invited Exhibition of Distinguished American Painters, March 2-21, 1927
      Fifth Annual Exhibition of Living American Etchers, Dec. 7-24, 1927
      Norse Pictorial Weavings by Mrs. Berthea Aske Bergh, April 6-29, 1928
      Members' Annual Exhibition, Feb. 8-29, 1928
      Sixth Annual Exhibition of Living American Etchers, Feb. 13-March 8, 1928
      Exhibition of Decorative Arts, March 8-31, 1928
      Junior Artist Members, April 4-20, 1928
      Members' Annual Exhibition, Jan. 8-Feb. 1, 1929
      Loan Exhibition of Italian Primitives from the Collection of Richard M. Hurd, March 1929
      Junior Artist Members, April 3-26, 1929
      Summer Exhibition of Painter Life Members, May 1-Oct. 1, 1929
      Exhibition of Decorative Arts, Dec. 4-26, 1929
      Members' Annual Exhibition, Jan. 8-Feb. 1, 1930
      Seventh Annual Exhibition of Living American Etchers, Feb. 5-28, 1930
      Junior Artist Members, March 5-28, 1930
      Members' Exhibition, April 16-Sept. 30, 1930
      Eighth Annual Exhibition of Living American Etchers, Dec. 3-26, 1930
      New York Water Color Club Exhibition, April 1-25, 1931
      Gramercy Park Centenary Celebration Exhibition, May 2-29, 1931
      Members' Annual Exhibition, Jan. 7-Feb. 6, 1931
      Junior Artists, March 4-27, 1931
      Members' Exhibition, June 3-Oct. 1, 1931
      Members' Exhibition, Jan. 6-13, 1932
      Exhibition of Drawings by Artist Members, Feb. 3-27, 1932
      Junior Artist Members, March 2-26, 1932
      Exhibition and Auction of Works of Art by Artist Members, March 13-April 15, 1932
      Exhibition by a Group of New York Art Schools, April 20-30. 1932
      Members' Exhibition, May 4-Oct. 1, 1932
    - Volume 8, cont. (Reel 4266, Frame 7-60)
    - Volume 9, 1933-1937 (Reel 4266, Frame 62-186)
      Members' Annual Exhibition, Jan. 4-27, 1933
      Junior Artist Members, March 1-31, 1933
      Society of Illustrators, April 5-22, 1933
      Members Exhibition, May 3-Oct. 1, 1933
      Memorial Exhibition, Group of Former Painter and Sculptor Members: Max Bohm, Emil Carlsen, Charles Hawthorne, Robert Henri, Karl Bitter, Solon Borglum, Daniel Chester French, Edmund Quinn, Jan. 31-March 2, 1934
      Junior Artist Members, March 7-29, 1934
      Thirty-second Annual Exhibition of the Society of Illustrators, April 4-27, 1934
      Members' Exhibition of Small Paintings and Sculpture, May 2-30, 1934
      Members' Annual Exhibition, Jan. 9-Feb. 1, 1935
      Members' No-Jury Exhibition, Feb. 6-March 2, 1935
      Junior Artist Members, March 6-29, 1935
      Loan Exhibition of Works of Art owned by Artist Members, April 3-27, 1935
      Members' Annual Exhibition, Jan. 8-31, 1936
      Junior Artist Members, March 4-27, 1936
      Exhibition of Neighboring Art Organizations, April 1-May 1, 1936
      First Annual Exhibition of Pictorial Photography, by Pictorial Forum, May 6-30, 1936
      Members' Annual Exhibition, Jan. 6-29, 1937
      Exhibition by the Younger Artists Group, March 3-26, 1937
      Second Exhibition of Neighboring Art Organizations, March 31-April 28, 1937
    - Volume 10, 1937-1940 (Reel 4266, Frame 187-397)
      Members' Exhibition of Small Paintings, in Black and White, Dec. 8-25, 1937
      Members' Annual Exhibition, Jan. 12-Feb., 1938
      Third Exhibition of Neighboring Art Organizations, March 14-April 2, 1938
      Exhibition of the Younger Artists Group, April 6-20, 1938
      Exhibition of a Group of Former Painter and Sculptor Members, Jan. 12-27, 1939
      Members' Annual Exhibition, Feb. 1-25, 1939
      Flower Paintings, March 1-31, 1939
      Fourth Annual Exhibition of Neighboring Art Organizations, April 5-21, 1939
      Annual Junior Members' Exhibition, May 10-24, 1939
      Selected Works by Deceased Artists from the National Arts Club's Permanent Collection, June-Oct. 1939
      Special Exhibition of the Paintings of Junior Members, Oct. 18-28, 1939
      Christmas Sale of Paintings, Drawing, Photographs, and Sculpture by Junior Members, Dec. 4-25, 1939
      Members' Annual Exhibition, Jan. 3-19, 1940
      Distinguished Exhibition of the Work of Living American Painters, Non-Members, Jan. 24-Feb. 9, 1940
      Ceramics, Feb. 14-29, 1940
      Annual Junior Members' Exhibition, April 3-19, 1940
      Flower and Still Life Paintings, April 24-May 3, 1940
  - Clippings, 1912-1940, 9.3:
    In addition to clippings, some volumes in this subseries also contain a small number of photographs and catalogs of commercial galleries in New York City.
    - Volume 11, 1912-1917 (Reel 4266, Frame 398-629)
    - Volume 12, 1916-1926 (Reel 4266, Frame 631-792)
    - Volume 12, 1916-1926, cont. (Reel 4267, Frame 7-367)
    - Volume 13, 1925-1928 (Reel 4267, Frame 368-908)
    - Volume 14, 1929-1932 (Reel 4267, Frame 910-1149)
    - Volume 14, 1929-1932, cont. (Reel 4268, Frame 7-316)
    - Volume 15, 1932-1933 (Reel 4268, Frame 317-502)
    - Volume 16, 1934-1936 (Reel 4268, Frame 503-659)
    - Volume 17, 1936-1940 (Reel 4268, Frame 660-935)
Indexes
Index 1: Annotated List of National Arts Club Exhibitions, 1899-1960, undated
* = photographs included with records of NAC (See pp. 22-23 for reel and frame numbers)
+ = photograph in NAC album (See pp. 24 for reel and frame numbers)
x = catalog, checklist, or printed announcement included with NAC printed matter
s = copy of catalog in NAC scrapbook (volume number noted, see pp. 27-32 for reel and frame numbers of each volume)
Microfilm reel and frame numbers (e.g.: N134:416-419) are cited below for NAC catalogs appearing in other collections within the Archives of American Art.
Date Exhibition
Oct. 30 *, 1899 House Warming, Exhibition of American Gold and Silver Work
Nov. 13-18, 1899 Tenth Exhibition of the Woman's Art Club; Reception to Miss Cecilia Beaux (N134:416-419)
Nov. 27-Dec. 10, 1899 Art Pottery, American, Oriental, and European (N134:407-415)
Dec. 23-Jan. 8, 1899 Exhibition of Small Bronzes (N134:437-443)
Jan. 13, 1900 Exhibition of Photographs, works by members of the Society of Mural Painters
Jan. 29, 1900 Design for Street Refuge, shown by New York Municipal Art Society
Feb. 5-22, 1900 Exhibition of Embroideries and Native Rugs (N134:420-425)
Feb. 24-Mar. 10, 1900 John Leslie Breck Memorial Exhibition (N443:703-708; N551:719-724)
Mar. 24-Apr. 14, 1900 Pastel Exhibition, American Work
Apr., 1900 Old and Modern Japanese Prints
Apr. 14-21, 1900 Ernest Tarleton Memorial Exhibition
Apr. 21-May 3, 1900 Exhibition of Color Reproductions, American and European
May 10-21, 1900 American Art Leatherwork (N134:432-426)
May 24-30, 1900 Small Exhibition of Japanese Water Colors
May 31-June 14, 1900 William Hamilton Gibson Memorial Exhibition
June, 1900 New York Municipal Art Society Competition
Nov. 28-Dec. 19 x, 1900 Arts and Crafts (N134:421-431)
Jan., 1901 Birds and Beasts in Art
Feb., 1901 Art Leatherwork and Objects Relating to the Hearth
Mar., 1901 Works by the Society of Mural Painters
Apr., 1901 Books and Bookmaking
Apr., 1901 Howard Walter, Water Colors Taken in Europe
May, 1901 Glass in the Arts
May, 1901 Memorial to John A. Fraser, His Paintings
May-Nov., 1901 Arts and Crafts in the Liberal Arts Building, Pan-American Pacific Exhibition, Buffalo, N.Y.
June-Sept., 1901 Sculpture, Oil Paintings, Pastels, Water Colors, and Objects of Industrial Art by Members of the Club
Oct., 1901 Memorial Window for the Ames Family by John La Farge
Nov., 1901 Annual Exhibition of Paintings and Sculpture by the Woman's Art Club
Dec., 1901 Objects Shown at the Pan-American Pacific Exposition
Jan., 1902 Ecclesiastical Art
Feb., 1902 Art Objects Relating to Civic Art, under the auspices of the Municipal Art Society
Mar., 1902 American Pictorial Photographs, shown by the Photo-Secession
Mar. 26-Apr. 21, 1902 Fourth Annual Exhibition of the National Sculpture Society (N551:725-729; N134:446-451)
May, 1902 Pictures of "Womanhood"
May, 1902 Memorial Window for Baltimore by D. Maitland Armstrong; Memorial Window for Wells College by Mrs. Ella Condie Lamb June Window in Stained Glass, Memorial to Julia Doane, Chicago, by John La Farge
Oct., 1902 Collection of Objects in Metal; Artistic Bird Cages lent by A. W. Drake, Esq.
Nov., 1902 Annual Exhibition by the Woman's Art Club
Nov., 1902 Paintings by Four Western Artists, Messrs. Duveneck, Steele, Meakin and Sharp, through the courtesy of the Cincinnati Museum Association
Dec., 1902 Designs Submitted for Competition for the Emblem of the Louisiana Purchase Exposition
Jan. s, 1903 Portraits of Napoleon, lent by John Leonard Dudley, Jr., Esq. (volume 4)
Jan., 1903 "Autumn," Stained Glass Window for the country residence of William C. Whitney, by John La Farge
Feb., 1903 Eskimo and Arctic Objects, with Paintings from the Arctic and Antarctic Circles by Frank Wilbert Stokes
Mar., 1903 Objects of Municipal Art
Apr., 1903 Examples of Ideal Art by American Artists
May, 1903 Sculptures by Rodin, Roche, and Rivere, belonging to Miss Lois Fuller
May, 1903 Portraits and other Paintings by American Artists of the Colonial and Early Periods
June-Oct., 1903 Summer Exhibition of Paintings, Water Colors, and Sculpture by Members of the Club
Nov., 1903 Jewelry and Precious Stones, Modern, Old and Oriental
Dec. 1-14, 1903 Thirteenth Annual Exhibition of the Woman's Art Club (N134:452-456)
Dec., 1903 Stained Glass Window, designed by Miss Mary E. Tillinghast
Dec., 1903 Sketches for the Sculpture at the Louisiana Purchase Exposition, shown by the National Sculpture Society
Jan. 5-16 s, 1904 Loan Exhibition of Pictures by Eminent American Painters (N134:426-464, and volume 4)
Jan. 5-16 s, 1904 Loan Exhibition of Pictures by Robert Henri, William Glackens, George Luks, Arthur B. Davies, and Maurice Prendergast (volume 4)
Feb., 1904 Pictures by Contemporary American Artists
Mar. 2-15, 1904 Loan Exhibition of Pictures by American Figure Painters (N50:471-472; N134:460-461)
Mar., 1904 Annual Exhibition of Objects of Municipal Art
Apr. 5-15 s, 1904 Loan Exhibition of Pictures by Some Boston Artists (N443:713-715, and volume 4)
Apr. 19-30 s, 1904 Loan Exhibition of Pictures by Old Masters, lent by the Messrs. Durand-Ruel (N443:711-712; N134:462-464, and volume 4)
May 3-14 s, 1904 Oil Paintings, Water Colors, and Drawings by John La Farge, N.A. (volume 4)
May, 1904 Photographs of Paintings by Old Italian Masters, under the auspices of the Library Committee
Oct., 1904 Work of Holders of the Lazarus and Reinhart Scholarships executed while at the American Academy in Rome
Nov., 1904 "The Moral and Divine Law," painting by John La Farge
Nov., 1904 Exhibition by Members of the Nippon-Bijitsuin (Japanese Art Academy)
Jan., 1905 Exhibition by the Lyme Group of Painters
Feb., 1905 "Old Masters" and Aphrodite
Feb., 1905 Pictures by Some Boston Artists
Mar., 1905 Annual Exhibition of the Municipal Art Society of New York
Apr., 1905 Artistic and Commercial Posters, under the Auspices of the Municipal Art Society
Apr., 1905 Textiles and Ceramics
Oct., 1905 "Out of Doors" as Seen by Various Artists
Nov., 1905 Color Prints by S. Arlent-Edwards
Dec., 1905 American Indians as Seen by the Artist and the Artist Photographer
Jan., 1906 Birds and Beasts in Art
Feb., 1906 Miniatures
Mar., 1906 Fifth Annual Exhibition of the Municipal Art Society
Mar., 1906 Exhibition by the Alumni of Cooper Institute
Apr. 2-14 s, 1906 Municipal Art Society Exhibit of Poster Designs (volume 4)